Guide to the Small Towns Institute Records 1956-2002 (bulk 1969-1997)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Subject files, 1969-1998; II
  - Farmers Market, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 36-4)
  - Farmland Preservation, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 36-5)
  - Farmland Preservation, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 36-6)
  - Farmland Preservation, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 36-7)
  - Farmland Preservation, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 36-8)
  - Farmland Preservation, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 37-1)
  - Festivals, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 37-2)
  - Fire, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 37-3)
  - Fire, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 37-4)
  - Fire Departments – Volunteer, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 37-5)
  - Fire Safety, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 37-6)
  - Floods and Floodplains, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 38-1)
  - Folklore, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 38-2)
  - Food, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 39-1)
  - Future, 1978-1990 (Box-folder 39-2)
  - Gardens, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 39-3)
  - Genealogy (Box-folder 39-4)
  - George, Henry – Land and Tax Philosophy, 1991 (Box-folder 39-5)
  - Great Plains, 1990 (Box-folder 39-6)
  - Growth, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 39-7)
  - Growth, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 39-8)
  - Growth, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 40-1)
  - Growth – “Coping with Growth" publication, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 40-2)
  - Growth Management – Kitsap County, 1985 (Box-folder 40-3)
  - Handicapped, 1972-1985 (Box-folder 40-4)
  - Hazardous Wastes, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 40-5)
  - Hazardous Wastes, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 40-6)
  - Health Care, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 41-1)
  - Health Care, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 41-2)
  - Health Care, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 41-3)
  - Health Care, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 41-4)
  - Health Care – “Commitment" publication, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 41-5)
  - Health Care – Doctor searches, 1983-1991 (Box-folder 41-6)
  - Health Care – Mental Health, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 41-7)
  - Health Clinic – Othello, Washington, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 41-8)
  - Historical Preservation, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 42-1)
  - Historical Preservation, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 42-2)
  - Historical Preservation, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 42-3)
  - Historical Preservation, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 43-1)
  - Historical Preservation, 1976-1989 (Box-folder 43-2)
  - Historical Preservation, Albia, Iowa, 1971 (Box-folder 43-3)
  - Historical Preservation – Battlefields, 1992 (Box-folder 43-4)
  - Historical Preservation – Centralia, Washington, 1987 (Box-folder 43-5)
  - Historical Preservation – Corning, New York, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 43-6)
  - Historical Preservation – Downtown, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 43-7)
  - Historical Preservation – Downtown, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 43-8)
  - Historical Preservation – Downtown, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 43-9)
  - Historical Preservation – Downtown, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 43-10)
  - Historical Preservation – Downtown, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 44-1)
  - Historical Preservation – Easements, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 44-2)
  - Historical Preservation – Education, Secondary Schools, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 44-3)
  - Historical Preservation – Effects on Business in Texas, 1988 (Box-folder 44-4)
  - Historical Preservation – Essex, New York, 1987 (Box-folder 44-5)
  - Historical Preservation – Federal Tax Laws, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 44-6)
  - Historical Preservation – Federal Tax Laws, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 44-7)
  - Historical Preservation – Federal Tax Laws, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 44-8)
  - Historical Preservation – Home and Building Tours, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 44-9)
  - Historical Preservation – Information Newsletters for National Trust, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 45-1)
  - Historical Preservation – Information Newsletters for National Trust, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 45-2)
  - Historical Preservation – Information Newsletters for National Trust, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 45-3)
  - Historical Preservation – Local Ordinance and Commission, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 45-4)
  - Historical Preservation – Local Ordinance and Commission, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 45-5)
  - Historical Preservation – Leesburg, Virginia, 1978 (Box-folder 45-6)
  - Historical Preservation – Lexington, Virginia, 1982 (Box-folder 45-7)
  - Historical Preservation – Marshall, Michigan, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 45-8)
  - Historical Preservation – Meridian, Mississippi, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 45-9)
  - Historical Preservation – National Trust, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 46-1)
  - Historical Preservation – National Trust, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 46-2)
  - Historical Preservation – National Trust, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 46-3)
  - Historical Preservation – National Trust, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 46-4)
  - Historical Preservation – National Trust, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 46-5)
  - Historical Preservation – National Trust, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 46-6)
  - Historical Preservation – National Trust, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 46-7)
  - Historical Preservation – Rugby, Tennessee, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 47-1)
  - Historical Preservation – Single Building Use, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 47-2)
  - Historical Preservation – Single Building Use, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 47-3)
  - Historical Preservation – Single Building Use, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 47-4)
  - Historical Preservation – Technical, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 47-5)
  - Historical Preservation – Urban, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 47-6)
  - Historical Preservation – Wallace, Idaho, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 47-7)
  - Home Occupations, 1991 (Box-folder 48-1)
  - Housing, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 48-2)
  - Housing, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 48-3)
  - Housing, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 48-4)
  - Housing, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 48-5)
  - Housing, 1977-1990 (Box-folder 48-6)
  - Housing – Canadian Programs, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 48-7)
  - Housing – Federal Programs, 1979-1991 (Box-folder 49-1)
  - Housing – Federal Programs, 1979-1991 (Box-folder 49-2)
  - Housing – Rehabilitation in Peekskill, New York, 1982 (Box-folder 49-3)
  - Housing – Single Families, 1985-1992 (Box-folder 49-4)
  - Housing – Suburbs, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 49-5)
  - Housing – State Assistance, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 49-6)
  - Human Services, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 49-7)
  - Industrial Development, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 50-1)
  - Indian-Americans, 1980-1993 (Box-folder 50-2)
  - Infrastructure, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 50-3)
  - Infrastructure, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 50-4)
  - Job Development, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 50-5)
  - Job Development, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 50-6)
  - Job Development, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 50-7)
  - Labor Organizing, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 50-8)
  - Land Ownership, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 51-1)
  - Land Trusts, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 51-2)
  - Land Use Planning, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 51-3)
  - Landscape, 1990 (Box-folder 51-4)
  - Land Reform, 1972-1987 (Box-folder 51-5)
  - Land Use Panning, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 51-6)
  - Land Use Panning, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 51-7)
  - Land Use Panning, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 51-8)
  - Leadership Day, 1989 (Box-folder 51-9)
  - Literature – Small Town Orientation, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 51-10)
  - Logging and Lumber Industry, 1980-1988 (Box-folder 52-1)
  - Logging and Lumber Industry, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 52-2)
  - Mediation, Community, 1986 (Box-folder 52-3)
  - Malls, 1976-1988 (Box-folder 52-4)
  - Management, 1976-1984 (Box-folder 52-5)
  - Migration, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 52-6)
  - Mining, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 52-7)
  - Minority Groups, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 52-8)
  - Minority Groups, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 53-1)
  - Mobile Homes, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 53-2)
  - Mobile Homes, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 53-3)
  - Mobile Homes, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 53-4)
  - Mobile Homes – Data on Manufacture, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 53-5)
  - Mobile Homes – Finance, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 53-6)
  - Mobile Homes – Zoning, 1982-1992 (Box-folder 53-7)
  - Motion Picture, 1974 (Box-folder 53-8)
  - Municipal Management, 1975-1999 (Box-folder 54-1)
  - Municipal Management, 1975-1999 (Box-folder 54-2)
  - Municipal Management, 1975-1999 (Box-folder 54-3)
  - Municipal Management – Canada, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 54-4)
  - Municipal Management – Circuit Riders, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 54-5)
  - Municipal Management – City Clerk, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 54-6)
  - Municipal Management – Cost Cutting (Box-folder 55-1)
  - Municipal Management – Finances, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 55-2)
  - Municipal Management – Finances, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 55-3)
  - Municipal Management – Finances, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 55-4)
  - Municipal Management – Personnel, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 55-5)
  - Museums, 1967-1981 (Box-folder 55-6)
  - Museums, 1967-1981 (Box-folder 56-1)
  - Museums, Brattleboro, Vermont, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 56-2)
  - Neighborhood, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 56-3)
  - Networking, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 56-4)
  - New Towns, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 56-5)
  - Newsletters – Community (Box-folder 56-6)
  - Newsletters – Far Out, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 56-7)
  - Newsletters – Far Out, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 56-8)
  - Newsletters – Municipal, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 56-9)
  - Newsletters – Small Towns (Box-folder 56-10)
  - Noise, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 57-1)
  - North Bonneville, Washington, 1977-1984 (Box-folder 57-2)
  - Open Space Preservation, 1972-1985 (Box-folder 57-3)
  - Oral History, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 57-4)
  - Oral History, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 57-5)
  - Parking and Regulations, 1986 (Box-folder 57-6)
  - Parks, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 57-7)
  - Parks, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 57-8)
  - Parks Department – Sterling, Illinois, 1985 (Box-folder 57-9)
  - Pets, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 58-1)
  - Pets, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 58-2)
  - Pets, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 58-3)
  - Pets, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 58-4)
  - Pets, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 58-5)
  - Planned Communities – PUDs, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 58-6)
  - Planned Communities – PUDs, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 58-7)
  - Planning – Bay, Maine, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 59-1)
  - Planning Aide – Town and County Planning Association, 1986 (Box-folder 59-2)
  - Planning Commission, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 59-3)
  - Planning – Comprehensive Plans, 1979 (Box-folder 59-4)
  - Planning – State Organizations (Box-folder 59-5)
  - Pollution, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 59-6)
  - Post Office, 1981 (Box-folder 59-7)
  - Poverty, 1970-2000 (Box-folder 59-8)
  - Poverty, 1970-2000 (Box-folder 59-9)
  - Quality of Life, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 59-10)
  - Radio – Community Radio Stations, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 59-11)
  - Rails to Trails, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 59-12)
  - Rails to Trails, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 60-1)
  - Rails to Trails, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 60-2)
  - Railroads, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 60-3)
  - Recreation, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 61-1)
  - Recreation, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 61-2)
  - Recreation, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 61-3)
  - Recreation, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 61-4)
  - Recreation, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 61-5)
  - Recreation – Skiing, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 61-6)
  - Recreation – Skiing, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 61-7)
  - Records Management, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 62-1)
  - Recycling, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 62-2)
  - Recycling, 1975-1992 (Box-folder 62-3)
  - Relocation Services to Small Towns, 1993 (Box-folder 62-4)
  - Rural America, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 62-5)
  - Rural Development, 1975-2000 (Box-folder 62-6)
  - Rural Development, 1975-2000 (Box-folder 62-7)
  - Rural Development, 1975-2000 (Box-folder 62-8)
  - Rural Electrification, 1982 (Box-folder 63-1)
  - Rural Policy, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 63-2)
  - Rural Policy, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 63-3)
  - Schools, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 63-4)
  - Senior Citizens, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 63-5)
  - Senior Citizens, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 63-6)
  - Senior Citizens – GeronTopics Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 63-7)
  - Servers, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 63-8)
  - Servers, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 64-1)
  - Sewage Treatment, 1981 (Box-folder 64-2)
  - Shopping Centers, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 64-3)
  - Shopping Centers, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 64-4)
  - Shopping Centers, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 64-5)
  - Shopping Centers – Discount Stores / WalMart, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 64-6)
  - Shopping Centers – Ellensburg, Washington, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 64-7)
  - Shopping Malls – Oberlin, Ohio, 1990 (Box-folder 64-8)
  - Shorelines, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 65-1)
  - Sidewalks, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 65-2)
  - Signs, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 65-3)
  - Signs, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 65-4)
  - Sludge Management, 1980-1993 (Box-folder 65-5)
  - Small Decline, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 65-6)
  - Small Decline, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 65-7)
  - Small Towns – General, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 66-1)
  - Small Towns – General, 1976-1990 (Box-folder 66-2)
  - Smoking, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 66-3)
  - Social Services, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 66-4)
  - Social Services, 1977-1989 (Box-folder 66-5)
  - Soil Conservation, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 66-6)
  - Soil Conservation, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 66-7)
  - Soil Conservation, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 66-8)
  - Solid Waste Management, 1975-1990 (Box-folder 67-1)
  - Solid Waste Management, 1975-1990 (Box-folder 67-2)
  - States – Alabama, 1974-1989 (Box-folder 68-1)
  - States – Alaska, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 68-2)
  - States – Arizona, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 68-3)
  - States – Arkansas, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 68-4)
  - States – California, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 68-5)
  - States – Colorado, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 68-6)
  - States – Colorado, 1975-1989 (Box-folder 68-7)
  - States – Connecticut, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 68-8)
  - States – Delaware, 1983 (Box-folder 68-9)
  - States – District of Columbia, 1978-1988 (Box-folder 68-10)
  - States – Florida, 1987 (Box-folder 68-11)
  - States – Hawaii, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 69-1)
  - States – Idaho, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 69-2)
  - States – Illinois, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 69-3)
  - States – Indiana, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 69-4)
  - States – Iowa, 1971-1989 (Box-folder 69-5)
  - States – Kansas, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 69-6)
  - States – Kentucky, 1984 (Box-folder 69-7)
  - States – Louisiana, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 69-8)
  - States – Maine, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 69-9)
  - States – Michigan, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 69-10)
  - States – Maryland, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 69-11)
  - States – Massachusetts, 1973-1987 (Box-folder 69-12)
  - States – Minnesota, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 69-13)
  - States – Minnesota, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 69-14)
  - States – Mississippi, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 70-1)
  - States – Missouri (Box-folder 70-2)
  - States – Montana, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 70-3)
  - States – Nebraska, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 70-4)
  - States – Nevada, 1986 (Box-folder 70-5)
  - States – New Hampshire, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 70-6)
  - States – New Jersey, 1986 (Box-folder 70-7)
  - States – New Mexico, 1978-1990 (Box-folder 70-8)
  - States – New York, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 70-9)
  - States – North Carolina, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 70-10)
  - States – North Dakota, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 70-11)
  - States – Ohio, 1974-1993 (Box-folder 71-1)
  - States – Oklahoma, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 71-2)
  - States – Oregon, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 71-3)
  - States – Pennsylvania, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 71-4)
  - States – Puerto Rico, 1986 (Box-folder 71-5)
  - States – Rhode Island, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 71-6)
  - States – South Carolina, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 71-7)
  - States – South Dakota, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 71-8)
  - States – Tennessee, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 71-9)
  - States – Texas, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 71-10)
  - States – Utah, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 71-11)
  - States – Vermont, 1972-1985 (Box-folder 72-1)
  - States – Vermont, 1972-1985 (Box-folder 72-2)
  - States – Washington, 1958-1991 (Box-folder 72-3)
  - States – Washington, 1958-1991 (Box-folder 72-4)
  - States – Washington, Ellensburg, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 72-5)
  - States – Washington, Historic, 1956-1985 (Box-folder 72-6)
  - States – West Virginia, 1991 (Box-folder 73-1)
  - States – Wisconsin, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 73-2)
  - States – Wyoming, 1973-1988 (Box-folder 73-3)
  - States – Canada, 1971-1991 (Box-folder 73-4)
  - States – Canada, 1971-1991 (Box-folder 73-5)
  - States – Europe, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 73-6)
  - South, The, 1975-1994 (Box-folder 73-7)
  - Streetscapes, 1980 (Box-folder 74-1)
  - Suburbs, 1975-1986 (Box-folder 74-2)
  - Surveys, 1971-1988 (Box-folder 74-3)
  - Surveys, 1971-1988 (Box-folder 74-4)
  - Sustainable Development, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 74-5)
  - Swimming Pools, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 74-6)
  - Swimming Pools, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 74-7)
  - Taxes, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 74-8)
  - Taxes, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 74-9)
  - Technology (Box-folder 75-1)
  - Telecommunications – Bloomsburg, Pennsylvania, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 75-2)
  - Theatres, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 75-3)
  - Theatres, 1977-1985 (Box-folder 75-4)
  - Theme Towns – Leavenworth, Washington, 1985 (Box-folder 75-5)
  - Town Consolidation, 1976-1997 (Box-folder 75-6)
  - Town / Gown Relationship, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 75-7)
  - Tourism, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 75-8)
  - Tourism, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 75-9)
  - Tourism, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 76-1)
  - Tourism, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 76-2)
  - Tourism, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 76-3)
  - Tourism, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 76-4)
  - Tourism, 1972-1990 (Box-folder 76-5)
  - Tourism – Canada, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 76-6)
  - Tourism – Canada, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 76-7)
  - Tourism – Eco-Tourism, 1993 (Box-folder 77-1)
  - Tourism – Maryland, 1987 (Box-folder 77-2)
  - Tourism – New York, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 77-3)
  - Tourism – Rhode Island, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 77-4)
  - Tourism – Texas, 1896-2002 (Box-folder 77-5)
  - Tourism Promotion – Grand Rapids, Minnesota, 1986 (Box-folder 77-6)
  - Trails (Box-folder 77-7)
  - Transferable Development Rights, 1976 (Box-folder 77-8)
  - Transportation, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 77-9)
  - Transportation, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 78-1)
  - Transportation, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 78-2)
  - Transportation – Rural Rides, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 78-3)
  - Trees – Urban Forestry - Elm Trees, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 78-4)
  - Trees – Urban Forestry – Marshall, Michigan, 1980 (Box-folder 78-5)
  - Urban Forestry, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 79-1)
  - Urban Forestry, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 79-2)
  - Urban Forestry, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 79-3)
  - Urban Forestry – “Wood Words", 1985-1986 (Box-folder 79-4)
  - Urban Development Action Grants, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 79-5)
  - Urban Policy, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 79-6)
  - Urban Policy, 1969-1986 (Box-folder 79-7)
  - Urban Renewal, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 80-1)
  - Volunteers, 1981-1994 (Box-folder 80-2)
  - Volunteers, 1981-1994 (Box-folder 80-3)
  - Water – “Rural Water Notes", 1975-1978 (Box-folder 80-4)
  - Water Quality, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 80-5)
  - Water Quality, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 80-6)
  - Water Quality, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 80-7)
  - Water Quality, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 81-1)
  - Waterfront, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 81-2)
  - Waterfront – Antwerp, Belgium, 1990 (Box-folder 81-3)
  - Watershed Planning and Wetlands, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 81-4)
  - Wilderness Preservation, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 81-5)
  - Women, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 81-6)
  - Women, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 82-1)
  - Youth, 1979-1992 (Box-folder 82-2)
  - Youth, 1979-1992 (Box-folder 82-3)
  - Zoning, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 82-4)
  - Zoning, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 82-5)
- Organization files, 1969-1998; III
  This series consists of alphabetically arranged files of private and government committees, councils, commissions, associations and organizations that supported conservation and preservation projects or programs (1969-1998). The series was organized by members of the Small Towns Institute and retained in its original order.
  - Advisory Council on Historic Preservation, 1981-1996 (Box-folder 83-1)
  - Advisory Council on Historic Preservation, 1981-1996 (Box-folder 83-2)
  - Affiliated State Arts Agencies of the Upper Northwest, 1984 (Box-folder 83-3)
  - Agricultural Accountability Project, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 83-4)
  - Agricultural Accountability Project, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 83-5)
  - Agricultural Land Fund, 1977 (Box-folder 83-6)
  - Alabama Community for the Humanities, 1981 (Box-folder 83-7)
  - Alabama Historical Commission, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 83-8)
  - Alaska Humanities Forum, 1982 (Box-folder 83-9)
  - Alliance for Cultural Democracy, 1984 (Box-folder 83-10)
  - “Alternate Roots", 1979-1982 (Box-folder 83-11)
  - Alternatives Christmas Catalogue, 1974 (Box-folder 83-12)
  - Amazing Life Games, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 83-13)
  - America the Beautiful Funds, 1974-1987 (Box-folder 83-14)
  - American Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1973 (Box-folder 84-1)
  - American Association for State and Local History, 1981 (Box-folder 84-2)
  - American Council for the Arts, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 84-3)
  - American Council for the Arts, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 84-4)
  - American Farmland Trust, 1981 (Box-folder 84-5)
  - American Federation of Labor Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1973 (Box-folder 84-6)
  - American Institute of Architects, 1974 (Box-folder 84-7)
  - American Land Reform, 1983 (Box-folder 84-8)
  - American Planning Association, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 84-9)
  - American Society of Agricultural Engineers, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 84-10)
  - American Society of Landscape Architects, 1981 (Box-folder 84-11)
  - American Society of Planning Officials, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 84-12)
  - Appalshop, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 84-13)
  - Archeology Conservancy, 1986 (Box-folder 84-14)
  - Arkansas Endowment for the Humanities, 1983 (Box-folder 84-15)
  - Association for a Paving Moratorium, 1994 (Box-folder 84-16)
  - Association for the Living Historical Farms and Museums (Box-folder 84-17)
  - Association of Municipalities of Ontario, 1985 (Box-folder 84-18)
  - Association of University Arts Administrators, 1982 (Box-folder 84-19)
  - Australian Rural Adjustment Unit, 1984 (Box-folder 84-20)
  - Ball Corporation, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 84-21)
  - Basic Livelihood Corporation, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 85-1)
  - Bishop Hill Heritage Association, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 85-2)
  - Black Hills Audubon Society, 1978 (Box-folder 85-3)
  - British Columbia Ministry of Municipal Affairs, 1982 (Box-folder 85-4)
  - Business Committee for the Arts, 1985 (Box-folder 85-5)
  - California Council for the Humanities, 1984 (Box-folder 85-6)
  - California Roadside Council, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 85-7)
  - Cambridge Systemics Inc., 1986 (Box-folder 85-8)
  - Campbell Center for Historic Preservation Studies, 1982 (Box-folder 85-9)
  - Canadian Institute of Planners, 1983 (Box-folder 85-10)
  - Catholic Rural Life Conference, 1975-2001 (Box-folder 85-11)
  - C.E.T.A., 1975 (Box-folder 85-12)
  - Center for Community Economic Development, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 85-13)
  - Center for Community Economic Development, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 85-14)
  - Center for Community Economic Development, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 85-15)
  - Center for Community Organization and Area Development, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 86-1)
  - Center for Metropolitan Planning and Research, 1981 (Box-folder 86-2)
  - Center for Rural Affairs – Walthill, Nebraska, 1974 (Box-folder 86-3)
  - Center for Rural Massachusetts, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 86-4)
  - Center for Small Town Research and Design, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 86-5)
  - Center of Agricultural and Rural Development, 1988 (Box-folder 86-6)
  - Centrum Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 86-7)
  - Chambers of Commerce, 1969-1987 (Box-folder 86-8)
  - City Hall Digest, 1981 (Box-folder 86-9)
  - Coalition for Rural America, 1972 (Box-folder 86-10)
  - Coalition for Rural America, 1972 (Box-folder 86-11)
  - Coalition for Rural America, 1972 (Box-folder 86-12)
  - Coalition for Rural Development, 1963-1974 (Box-folder 87-1)
  - Colorado Commission on the Humanities, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 87-2)
  - Colorado Innovation Center Denver Urban Observatory, 1982 (Box-folder 87-3)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 87-4)
  - Committee for the Future Inc., 1972-1974 (Box-folder 87-5)
  - Community Planning Association of Canada, 1976 (Box-folder 87-6)
  - Community Rehabilitation Training Center, 1983 (Box-folder 87-7)
  - Community Service Inc., 1975-1984 (Box-folder 87-8)